export default [
{
    id: 1,
    question: 'What is 1 ÷ 1 ?',
    answers: ['3','2','1','0'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [1, 0, 2, 3, 4]
},
{
    id: 2,
    question: 'What is 2 ÷ 1 ?',
    answers: ['2','3','1','0'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [0, 1, 2, 3, 4]
},
{
    id: 3,
    question: 'What is 2 ÷ 2 ?',
    answers: ['3','1','0','2'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [3, 2, 4, 5, 6]
},
{
    id: 4,
    question: 'What is 3 ÷ 1 ?',
    answers: ['3','1','2','0'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [2, 3, 4, 5, 6]
},
{
    id: 5,
    question: 'What is 3 ÷ 3 ?',
    answers: ['3','0','1','2'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [5, 4, 6, 7, 8]
},
{
    id: 6,
    question: 'What is 4 ÷ 1 ?',
    answers: ['2','4','5','6'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [4, 5, 6, 7, 8]
},
{
    id: 7,
    question: 'What is 4 ÷ 2 ?',
    answers: ['3','0','1','2'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [5, 6, 7, 8, 9]
},
{
    id: 8,
    question: 'What is 4 ÷ 4 ?',
    answers: ['1','2','3','0'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [8, 7, 9, 10, 11]
},
{
    id: 9,
    question: 'What is 5 ÷ 1 ?',
    answers: ['5','4','8','6'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [7, 8, 9, 10, 11]
},
{
    id: 10,
    question: 'What is 5 ÷ 5 ?',
    answers: ['2','1','0','3'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [10, 9, 11, 12, 13]
},
{
    id: 11,
    question: 'What is 6 ÷ 1 ?',
    answers: ['9','4','6','5'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [9, 10, 11, 12, 13]
},
{
    id: 12,
    question: 'What is 6 ÷ 2 ?',
    answers: ['0','2','1','3'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [10, 11, 12, 13, 14]
},
{
    id: 13,
    question: 'What is 6 ÷ 3 ?',
    answers: ['2','1','0','3'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [11, 12, 13, 14, 15]
},
{
    id: 14,
    question: 'What is 6 ÷ 6 ?',
    answers: ['3','1','0','2'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [14, 13, 15, 16, 17]
},
{
    id: 15,
    question: 'What is 7 ÷ 1 ?',
    answers: ['10','5','9','7'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [13, 14, 15, 16, 17]
},
{
    id: 16,
    question: 'What is 7 ÷ 7 ?',
    answers: ['0','3','1','2'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [16, 15, 17, 18, 19]
},
{
    id: 17,
    question: 'What is 8 ÷ 1 ?',
    answers: ['10','7','8','5'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [15, 16, 17, 18, 19]
},
{
    id: 18,
    question: 'What is 8 ÷ 2 ?',
    answers: ['5','6','7','4'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [16, 17, 18, 19, 20]
},
{
    id: 19,
    question: 'What is 8 ÷ 4 ?',
    answers: ['2','3','1','0'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [17, 18, 19, 20, 21]
},
{
    id: 20,
    question: 'What is 8 ÷ 8 ?',
    answers: ['0','2','1','3'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [20, 19, 21, 22, 23]
},
{
    id: 21,
    question: 'What is 9 ÷ 1 ?',
    answers: ['6','7','9','10'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [19, 20, 21, 22, 23]
},
{
    id: 22,
    question: 'What is 9 ÷ 3 ?',
    answers: ['0','1','3','2'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [20, 21, 22, 23, 24]
},
{
    id: 23,
    question: 'What is 9 ÷ 9 ?',
    answers: ['1','2','3','0'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [23, 24, 22, 21, 20]
},
{
    id: 24,
    question: 'What is 10 ÷ 1 ?',
    answers: ['9','7','10','12'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [22, 23, 24, 25, 26]
},
{
    id: 25,
    question: 'What is 10 ÷ 2 ?',
    answers: ['5','4','2','3'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [23, 24, 25, 26, 27]
},
{
    id: 26,
    question: 'What is 10 ÷ 5 ?',
    answers: ['1','0','2','3'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [24, 25, 26, 27, 28]
},
{
    id: 27,
    question: 'What is 10 ÷ 10 ?',
    answers: ['1','0','2','3'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [27, 26, 28, 29, 30]
},
]
